Thomas G. Paterson Papers
© 2003 University of Connecticut
- Series VI: Research materials, undated, 1839-1997
  - United States and Castro's Cuba
    - Anti-Batista activities in the U.S., 1957 September - November (Box 17:450)
    - Anti-Batists groups in Newark, September 1957-January 1960 (FBI reports), 1957-1960 (Box 17:451)
    - U.S.-Cuba, October, 1957, 1957 October (Box 17:452)
    - U.S.-Cuba, November, 1957, undated, 1957 October - December (Box 17:453)
    - Cuba, December, 1957, 1957 December (Box 17:454)
    - Anti-Batista activities in the U.S., undated, 1957-1958 (Box 17:455)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1958, undated, 1958-1959 (Box 17:456)
    - Anti-Batista groups in the U.S., 1958-1959, (FBI records), undated, 1958-1959 (Box 17:457)
    - Anti-Batista activities in New York, 1958-1959 (FBI records), undated, 1958-1959 (Box 17:458)
    - Cuba, January, 1958, 1958 January (Box 17:459)
    - Cuba, February, 1958, undated, 1958 January - April (Box 17:460)
    - John Foster Dulles' desk calendar, 1958 February 25 - April 1 (Box 17:461)
    - Cuba, 1958 March 3-31 (Box 17:462)
    - Herter telephone calls, (box 11, Herter Papers, Dwight D. Eisenhower Library (DDEL)), 1958 March 13-31 (Box 17:463)
    - Eisenhower telephone calls, March 13-March 31, 1958 (Whitman file, box 34, DDE diary series, DDE Papers, DDEL), 1958 March 13-31 (Box 17:464)
    - Dulles telephone calls, March 18-April 1, 1958 (boxes 8, 12, 13, Dulles Papers, DDEL), 1958 March 18 - April 1 (Box 17:465)
    - Cuba, April 1958, 1958 April (Box 17:466)
    - Anti-Batista groups in the U.S., (FBI records), undated, 1958 April - October (Box 17:467)
    - Cuba, May 1958, undated, 1956-1958 (Box 17:468)
    - Cuba, June 1958, undated, 1958 June (Box 17:469)
    - Kidnapping episode, June-July 1958, undated1958 June - July (Box 17:470)
    - Anti-Batista groups in Chicago, June 1958-December 1959 (FBI records), undated, 1958-1959 (Box 18:471)
    - Cuba, July 1958, 1958 July (Box 18:472)
    - Cuba, August 1958, 1958 August 1 - October 7 (Box 18:473)
    - Cuba, September 1958, 1958-1959 (Box 18:474)
    - Cuba, October 1958, undated, 1958 October - November (Box 18:475)
    - Anti-Batista groups in the U.S., November 1958 (FBI records), undated, 1958 November 14-25 (Box 18:476)
    - Cuba, November 1958, undated, 1958 November 7-29 (Box 18:477)
    - Cuba, December 1958, 1956 December - 1958 December (Box 18:478)
    - Cuba, December 1958, 1958-1961 (Box 18:479)
    - Senator Allen J. Ellender's notes on trip to Cuba, December 1958, 1958 December 8-18 (Box 18:480)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1959, undated, 1960-1983 (Box 18:481)
    - Anti-Batista groups in the U.S., December 1958-February, 1959 (FBI records), undated, 1958-1959 (Box 18:482)
    - Anti-Castro activities in Cuba (FBI records), undated, 1959 March - November (Box 18:483)
    - Cuban exiles (FBI records), 1959 July - December (Box 18:484)
    - Anti-Castro activities in the U.S., 1959 (FBI records), 1959 January - June (Box 18:485)
    - Anti-Castro activities in the U.S., 1959-1960 (FBI records), undated, 1959, 1978 (Box 18:486)
    - U.S.-Cuba, January, 1959 (early reactions to Castro victory), undated, 1959 January 1-15 (Box 18:487)
    - U.S.-Cuba, January, 1959 (early reactions to Castro victory), 1959 January 15-31 (Box 18:488)
    - Batista in exile: Dominican Republic and issue of entry into U.S., 1959 January 6 - July 30 (Box 18:489)
    - U.S.-Cuba, February, 1959, undated, 1959 January - February (Box 18:490)
    - NSC 5902/1 U.S Policy Toward Latin America, 1959 February (Box 19:491)
    - U.S.-Cuba, March, 1959, 1959 January - May (Box 19:492)
    - U.S.-Cuba, April, 1959, 1959 April - June (Box 19:493)
    - Castro trip to U.S., April, 1959, undated, 1959 February - July (Box 19:494)
    - Chiefs of Mission meeting, San Salvador, April 9-11, 1959, undated, 1959 April 24 (Box 19:495)
    - U.S.-Cuba, May, 1959, 1959 March - May (Box 19:496)
    - Organization of American States meeting, 1959 May 12-14 (Box 19:497)
    - U.S.-Cuba, June, 1959, undated, 1959 June 1-18 (Box 19:498)
    - U.S.-Cuba, June, 1959, 1959, June 20-30 (Box 19:499)
    - U.S.-Cuba, July, 1959, undated, 1959 June - July (Box 19:500)
    - U.S.-Cuba, July, 1959, 1959 July - August (Box 19:501)
    - U.S.-Cuba, August, 1959, 1959 August (Box 19:502)
    - U.S.-Cuba, undated, 1959 September (Box 19:503)
    - U.S.-Cuba, undated, 1959 October (Box 19:504)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1959 October 25 - November 17 (Box 19:505)
    - Current Basic United States Policy Towards Cuba, November, 1959, 1959 October 31 - November 9 (Box 19:506)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1959 November (Box 19:507)
    - U.S.-Cuba, undated, 1959 October - December (Box 20:508)
    - U.S.-Cuba, undated, 1960-1961 (Box 20:509)
    - Anti-Castro activities in the U.S. (FBI records), undated, 1960 (Box 20:510)
    - The issue of Cuba in the 1960 campaign, undated, 1960-1961 (Box 20:511)
    - Anti-Castro activities in the U.S., 1960-1961 (FBI records), undated, 1961 January - November (Box 20:512)
    - U.S.-Cuba, undated, 1960 January - February (Box 20:513)
    - Amoedo incident (January-February 1960), undated, 1960-1987 (Box 20:514)
    - Sugar legislation and the Cuban quota, January-October, 1960, undated, 1960 January - May (Box 20:515)
    - Sugar legislation and the Cuban quota, January-October, 1960, 1960-1962 (Box 20:516)
    - U.S.-Cuba, undated, 1960 February 1-11 (Box 20:517)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1960 February12 - March 21 (Box 20:518)
    - Eisenhower Good Will trip to Latin America (discussions with leaders about Cuba), undated, 1960 February - March (Box 20:519)
    - Mikoyan visit and Soviet-Cuban Trade Agreement, undated, 1960 February - March (Box 20:520)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1960 March 3-21 (Box 20:521)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1960 March - 1976 November (Box 20:522)
    - U.S.-Cuba, undated, 1960 April 1-12 (Box 20:523)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1960 April 13-29 (Box 20:524)
    - Attitudes of the Cuban People Toward the Castro Regime in the Late Spring of 1960, 1960 (Box 20:525)
    - U.S.-Cuba, undated, 1960 May (Box 21:526)
    - U.S.-Cuba, undated, 1960 June - July (Box 21:527)
    - Report and Recommendations on Cuba, Baggett report, 1960 June 21-23 (Box 21:528)
    - July 1960 crisis (oil properties, Soviet statement, etc.), undated, 1960 July 1-14 (Box 21:529)
    - July 1960 crisis (oil properties, Soviet statement, etc.), 1960 July - August (Box 21:530)
    - "Responsibility of the Cuban Government for Increased International Tensions in the Caribbean", July 15, 1960 (document from DDEL), 1960 July 15-August 5 (Box 21:531)
    - U.S.-Cuba, August, 1960, 1960-1986 (Box 21:532)
    - Organization of American States and Cuban Issue,1960 (San Jose Meeting, August, 1960), undated, 1960 March - September (Box 21:533)
    - Herbert Matthews trip to Cuba, August 8-15, 1960, undated, 1960 August 17 (Box 21:534)
    - U.S.-Cuba, September, 1960, 1950 September 1-October 17 (Box 21:535)
    - U.S.-Cuba, October, 1960, undated, 1960 October - November (Box 21:536)
    - Export Controls imposed, October, 1960, 1960 October - 1962 June (Box 21:537)
    - Export Control report, 4th quarter, 1960 (Box 21:538)
    - U.S.-Cuba, November, 1960, 1959-1960 (Box 21:539)
    - Revolt in Guatemala, November, 1960 (Cuban connection and role of trainees), 1960 November - December (Box 21:540)
    - U.S.-Cuba, December, 1960, undated. 1960-1961 (Box 21:541)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1961, undated, 1960-1961 (Box 21:542)
    - Export Control reports, 1961 (Box 21:543)
    - Anti-Castro group activities in U.S., 1961-1962, (FBI records), 1961-1978 (Box 21:544)
    - Geddes (prisoner) case, 1961-1963, undated, 1962-1963 (Box 21:545)
    - Break in diplomatic relations, January, 1961, undated, 1961 January - May (Box 21:546)
    - U.S.-Cuba, January, 1961 (other than break in diplomatic relations), undated, 1961 January - February (Box 21:547)
    - U.S.-Cuba, February, 1961, undated, 1961 January - March (Box 22:548)
    - U.S.-Cuba, March, 1961, 1961 February - May (Box 22:549)
    - April 1961: before the Bay of Pigs invasion, 1961 April - 1963 June (Box 22:550)
    - Bay of Pigs
      - Bay of Pigs invasion, April,1961, 1961 April - June (Box 22:551)
      - The press 1961, 1966, 1961-1982 (Box 22:552)
      - Various dissenters (Bowles, etc.), 1961 March - July (Box 22:553)
      - J. William Fulbright, 1961, undated, 1961-1983 (Box 22:554)
      - Bay of Pigs (general), undated, 1961-1974 (Box 22:555)
      - U.S. Military role, 1961-1975, undated, 1962-1984 (Box 22:556)
      - Taylor Committee Investigation of the Bay of Pigs, chapters 4-6, appendices and memoranda, 1961, undated (Box 22:557)
      - The Taylor Committee Investigation of the Bay of Pigs, Jack Pfeiffer (CIA) study, 1984 November 9 (Box 22:558)
      - After the Bay of Pigs Invasion: April, 1961, undated, 1961 April - June (Box 22:559)
    - U.S.-Cuba, May, 1961, 1961 April - June (Box 22:560)
    - NSC 2413 U.S. Policy Toward Cuba, 1961 May 4 (Box 22:561)
    - Bay of Pigs and Tractor Exchange, 1961
      - 1961 (general), undated, 1961-1981 (Box 22:562)
      - May, 1961, undated, 1959-1961 (Box 22:563)
      - June, 1961, undated, 1961-1963 (Box 22:564)
      - July-August, 1961, 1961 July - August (Box 22:565)
      - Gibson case (American prisoner), 1961 June - September (Box 22:566)
      - William D. Bishop Papers (given to Paterson) and interview, undated, 1961-1981 (Box 22:567)
      - Milton Eisenhower Papers, undated, 1961 May - June (Box 22:568)
      - Clarence M. Hansen Papers (given to Paterson), undated, 1961-1974 (Box 22:569)
      - J.B. Liljedahl Papers (given to Paterson), undated, 1961 May - June (Box 22:570)
      - Walter Reuther Papers, undated, 1961 May - July (Box 22:571)
      - Eleanor Roosevelt Papers/ "My Day" columns, undated, 1961 May - October (Box 22:572)
    - U.S. -Cuba, June, 1961, 1961 May - June (Box 23:573)
    - U.S.-Cuba, July-September, 1961, 1961 January - September (Box 23:574)
    - Bay of Pigs: Murphy article episode, 19612 August - October (Box 23:575)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1916 October - December (Box 23:576)
    - Export Control reports, 1962 (Box 23:577)
    - U.S.-Cuba, January-February, 1962, undated, 1962 January - March (Box 23:578)
    - Trade restrictions, January-November, 1962, 1962-1964 (Box 23:579)
    - Lansdale, The Cuba Project (overthrow of Cuban government), 1962 February 20 (Box 23:580)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1962 March - April (Box 23:581)
    - The Situation and Prospects in Cuba (CIA), 1962 March 21 (Box 23:582)
    - U.S.-Cuba, May-June, 1962, undated, 1962 April - June (Box 23:583)
    - Anti-Castro group activities in U.S., June 1962-April 1963 (FBI records), 1962-1978 (Box 23:584)
    - Cuban exile attacks against Cuba, June-November 1962 (FBI records), 1962 June - November (Box 23:585)
    - U.S.-Cuba, July-August, 1962, 1962 May - August (Box 23:586)
    - Roper Center (UConn) polling data on Cuban issues, 1962 August - December (Box 23:587)
    - U.S.-Cuba, September, 1962, undated (Box 23:588)
    - Udall trip to Russia, September, 1962, undated (Box 23:589)
    - U.S.-Cuba, October, 1962 (before the Cuban Missile Crisis), undated (Box 23:590)
    - Cuban Missile Crisis
      - Chronology of Cuban Missile Crisis, October 15-28, 1962, undated (Box 23:591)
      - Chronology and archival material of Cuban Missile Crisis, prepared by WGBH, 1986 (Box 23:592)
      - Cinclant Historical Account of Cuban Crisis, 1963 (Box 23:593)
      - The Cuban Missile Crisis, 1962, Department of State report, Frank A. Sieverts, undated, 1963 August 22 (Box 23:594)
      - Cuban Missile Crisis, 1962 (general), undated, 1961-1988 (Box 23:595)
      - Cuban Missile Crisis: October, 1962 high level meetings: proposals, memos, undated, 1962-1968 (Box 23:596)
      - CIA reports during the Missile Crisis, 1962, 1962 October 16-26 (Box 23:597)
      - Kennedy tapes: Cuban Missile Crisis meeting of October 16, 1962, 11:50 a.m.-12:47 p.m. (JFK Library), 1962 October 16 (Box 23:598)
      - Kennedy tapes: Cuban Missile Crisis meeting of October 16, 1962, 6:30 p.m.-7:55 p.m. (JFK Library), 1962 October 16 (Box 23:599)
      - Excomm and NSC (National Security Council) records of the action and minutes, Missile Crisis, 1962 October - December (Box 24:600)
      - Department of Defense news briefings, 1962 October 22-29 (Box 24:601)
      - LBJ notes on Missile Crisis meetings (LBJ Library), 1962 October 23-26 (Box 24:602)
      - Khruschev letter to Kennedy, October 26, 1962, 1962-1973 (Box 24:603)
      - Cuban Missile Crisis meetings, transcript, October 27, 1962 (JFK Library), 1962 October 27 (Box 24:604)
      - Canada and the missile Crisis, 1962 October - November (Box 24:605)
      - Cuban Missile Crisis: An Intelligence Gap?, undated, 1962 (Box 24:606)
      - Keating and the Cuban Missile Crisis: letters to Paterson, undated, 1962-1986 (Box 24:607)
      - Politics (election of 1962) and the missile Crisis, undated, 1962-1984 (Box 24:608)
      - Role of the U.S. Military, undated, 1962-1979 (Box 24:609)
      - U. Thant and United Nations role, undated, 1962-1964 (Box 24:610)
      - Sloan Foundation tapes 1-4, 1983 January 27-28 (Box 24:611)
      - Sloan Foundation tapes 5-7, undated, 1983 January 22-28 (Box 24:612)
      - Letters from participants to Paterson, 1984-1985 (Box 24:613)
    - U.S.-Cuba, November, 1962 (including Missile Crisis and its aftermath), 1961-1962 (Box 24:614)
    - Mikoyan in Cuba, November, 1962: post-Missile Crisis, 1962 October - December (Box 24:615)
    - Presidential statements on Cuba, November 1962-March, 1963, 1962-1963 (Box 24:616)
    - Castro's Subversive Capabilities (CIA), 1962 November 9 (Box 24:617)
    - Aberle case at Brandeis, 1963 March - June (Box 24:618)
    - U.S.-Cuba, December, 1962 (including Missile Crisis and aftermath), undated, 1962 December (Box 24:619)
    - Bay of Pigs prisoners exchange (1962), undated, 1962-1982 (Box 24:620)
    - 1962 prisoners exchange mss by Rudolph A. Clemen, Jr. of the American Red Cross, 1963-1982 (Box 24:621)
    - Background briefing with the President, Palm Beach, Florida, 1962 December 31 (Box 24:622)
    - U.S.-Cuba, undated, 1963 (Box 24:623)
    - Export Control reports, 1963 (Box 24:624)
    - Prospects for Re-establishing Relations With Cuba, Colonel Harry A. Paynter (NDU), 1963 (Box 24:625)
    - U.S.-Cuba, January, 1963, 1963 January - February (Box 24:626)
    - U.S.-Cuba, February, 1963, 1963 January - March (Box 24:627)
    - U.S.-Cuba, March, 1963, 1963 (Box 25:628)
    - Anti-Castro groups and attacks against Cuba, March-October, 1963 (FBI records), 1963-1978 (Box 25:629)
    - U.S. Policy on exile raids, March-December, 1963 (Box 25:630)
    - Cuban Training of Latin American Subversives (CIA), 1963 March 27 (Box 25:631)
    - U.S. -Cuba, April, 1963, 1961-1963 (Box 25:632)
    - Castro's trip to USSR, 1963 April - July (Box 25:633)
    - U.S.-Cuba, May, 1963, 1963 April - June (Box 25:634)
    - Report on the Situation of Political Prisoners and Their Relatives in Cuba (Organization of American States), 1963 May (Box 25:635)
    - U.S.-Cuba, June, 1963, undated, 1963 (Box 25:636)
    - Covert activities against Cuba, June-December,1963 (CIA and exiles), 1962-1978 (Box 25:637)
    - Covert activities against Cuba, June-December,1963 (CIA and exiles), 1963 August - December (Box 25:638)
    - U.S.-Cuba, July-September, 1963, 1963 April - September (Box 25:639)
    - U.S.-Cuba contacts for accommodation (Attwood), 1963-1964 (Box 25:640)
    - U.S.-Cuba, October-December, 1963, 1963 September - December (Box 25:641)
    - Herbert Matthews trip to Cuba and aftermath, October-December, 1963, 1963-1964 (Box 25:642)
    - Question of aid to Cuba after Hurricane Flora, 1963 October - 1964 April (Box 25:643)
    - Charles O. Porter interview with Fidel Castro, October 3, 1963, 1963 (Box 25:644)
    - Assassination of Kennedy and Cuba, November 1963-1964, 1963-1977 (Box 25:645)
    - Cuba, Venezuela, and arms cache, November, 1963-September, 1964, undated, 1963-1964 (Box 25:646)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1964, undated (Box 25:647)
    - Export Control reports, 1964 (Box 25:648)
    - U.S.-Cuba, January-February, 1964, undated, 1964-1965 (Box 25:649)
    - Guantanamo water crisis, undated, 1964 February (Box 25:650)
    - U.S.-Cuba, March, 1964, 1964 February - March (Box 26:651)
    - U.S.-Cuba, April-June, 1964, 1964 April - June (Box 26:652)
    - Survey of Latin America (Cuban portions), 1964 April 1 (Box 26:653)
    - U.S.-Cuba, July-August, 1964, 1960-1964 (Box 26:654)
    - Situation and Prospects in Cuba (CIA), 1964 August 5 (Box 26:655)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1964 September - November (Box 26:656)
    - U.S.-Cuba, December, 1964, undated, 1963-1965 (Box 26:657)
    - Che Guevara trip to Africa, December 1964-March 1965, 1965 January - April (Box 26:658)
    - Export Control reports, 1965 (Box 26:659)
    - Issue of Cuban subversion in Latin America, undated, 1965 January - May (Box 26:660)
    - Refugee agreement, airlift, and program, 1965-1968 (Box 26:661)
    - U.S.-Cuba, undated, 1965 January - March (Box 26:662)
    - Intelligence Handbook on Cuba (CIA), 1965 January 1 (Box 26:663)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1965 April - June (Box 26:664)
    - Dominican Republic and Cuba, undated (Box 26:665)
    - U.S.-Cuba, undated (Box 26:666)
    - U.S.-Cuba, October-December, 1965, undated (Box 26:667)
    - Issue of travel to Cuba, November-December 1965, undated (Box 26:668)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1966, undated (Box 26:669)
    - Export Control reports, undated (Box 26:670)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1967, undated (Box 26:671)
    - Export Control reports, undated (Box 26:672)
    - Cuban subversian in Venezuela and the Organization of American States, 1967 May - December (Box 26:673)
    - U.S.-Cuba, undated, 1968 (Box 26:674)
    - Export Control reports, 1968 (Box 26:675)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1969 January - May (Box 26:676)
    - Export Control reports, 1969 (Box 26:677)
    - U.S.-Cuba, undated, 1970 January - August (Box 26:678)
    - Export Control reports, 1970 (Box 26:679)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1971 January - August (Box 26:680)
    - Export Control reports, 1971 (Box 26:681)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1972 February - September (Box 26:682)
    - Export Control reports, 1972 (Box 26:683)
    - Congressional conference on U.S.-Cuban relations, Senate Building, Washington, D.C., 1972 April (Box 27:684)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1973, 1973 January - October (Box 27:685)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1974, 1974-1975 (Box 27:686)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1975, undated, 1975-1976 (Box 27:687)
    - Export Control reports, 1975-1977 (Box 27:688)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1976, undated, 1976 January - October (Box 27:689)
    - Senator Frank Church's trip to Cuba, August 1977, undated, 1977 August - November (Box 27:690)
    - Late 1970s: economic questions (trade, business claims), 1976-1979 (Box 27:691)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1977, undated (Box 27:692)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1978, 1970-1978 (Box 27:693)
    - U.S.-Cuba, 1979, 1979 (Box 27:694)
    - Research notes for U.S.-Cuba relations (Tray 9), organized by subject, 1950-1960 (Box 39-40)
    - Research notes for U.S.-Cuba relations (Tray 10), organized by subject, 1961 (Box 41)
  - Information on manuscript collections
    - Alabama, undated, 1967-1984 (Box 27:695)
    - Alaska, undated, 1983 December 19 (Box 27:696)
    - Arizona, undated (Box 27:697)
    - Arkansas, undated, 1981-1992 (Box 27:698)
    - California, undated, 1981-1986 (Box 27:699)
    - Canada, undated, 1988-1991 (Box 27:700)
    - Colorado, undated, 1993 March 11 (Box 27:701)
    - Connecticut: Yale, undated, 1973-1991 (Box 27:702)
    - Delaware, 1973-1981 (Box 27:703)
    - Florida, undated, 1983-1991 (Box 27:704)
    - Georgia, undated, 1983-1990 (Box 27:705)
    - Great Britain, undated, 1973-1986 (Box 27:706)
    - Idaho, 1983-1986 (Box 27:707)
    - Illinois, 1981-1984 (Box 27:708)
    - Indiana, undated, 1983 November 21-29 (Box 27:709)
    - Iowa (includes Hoover Presidential Library), undated, 1977-1984 (Box 27:710)
    - Kansas, undated, 1963-1983 (Box 27:711)
    - Kansas: Dwight D. Eisenhower Presidential Library, undated, 1973-1986 (Box 27:712)
    - Kentucky, 1983 December 9 (Box 27:713)
    - Louisiana, 1983-1991 (Box 27:714)
    - Maryland, undated, 1973--1985 (Box 27:715)
    - Michigan, undated, 1981-1984 (Box 27:716)
    - Michigan: Gerald Ford Presidential Library, 1982-1986 (Box 27:717)
    - Minnesota, undated, 1983 December 7-12 (Box 27:718)
    - Mississippi, undated (Box 27:719)
    - Missouri, undated, 1974-1984 (Box 27:720)
    - Montana, 1980-1984 (Box 27:721)
    - Nebraska, 1983-1984 (Box 27:722)
    - Nevada, 1983 December 2-19 (Box 27:723)
    - New England, undated, 1971-1990 (Box 27:724)
    - New Jersey, undated, 1981-1991 (Box 28:725)
    - New York, undated, 1951-1996 (Box 28:726)
    - North Carolina, undated, 1983-1984 (Box 28:727)
    - North Dakota, undated, 1983-1984 (Box 28:728)
    - Ohio, undated, 1983-1984 (Box 28:729)
    - Oklahoma, undated, 1983 July - December (Box 28:730)
    - Oregon, undated, 1974-1984 (Box 28:731)
    - Pennsylvania, undated, 1983-1985 (Box 28:732)
    - South Carolina, undated, 1983-1984 (Box 28:733)
    - South Dakota, undated, 1983-1984 (Box 28:734)
    - Texas (includes Lyndon B. Johnson Presidential Library), 1974-1989 (Box 28:735)
    - Utah, undated, 1983-1985 (Box 28:736)
    - Virginia, undated, 1970-1991 (Box 28:737)
    - Washington (state), 1986-1987 (Box 28:738)
    - Washington, D.C., undated, 1973-1996 (Box 28:739)
    - Wisconsin, undated, 1983-1984 (Box 28:740)
    - Wyoming, undated, 1993 April 20 (Box 28:741)
  - Mandatory review and Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) requests
    - CIA FOIA requests, 1982-1995 (Box 28:742)
    - Department of Defense, Navy and Army, undated, 1984-1992 (Box 28:743)
    - Department of State (and ACDA and NSC), undated, 1982-1986 (Box 28:744)
    - Department of State (and ACDA and NSC), 1986-1989 (Box 28:745)
    - FBI FOIA requests, undated, 1956-1986 (Box 28:746)
    - FBI FOIA requests, undated, 1986-1991 (Box 28:747)
    - National Security Council, undated, 1986-1989 (Box 28:748)
    - Treasury and FOIA Commerce, 1983-1992 (Box 28:749)
    - Dwight D. Eisenhower Library declassification -- MRS pending, undated, 1981-1995 (Box 28:750)
    - Gerald Ford Library -- MRS, 1986-1987 (Box 28:751)
    - John F. Kennedy Library -- MRS, undated, 1984-1997 (Box 28:752)
    - Lyndon B. Johnson Library
      - undated, 1984 March 7 - 1986 November 20 (Box 28:753)
      - 1987-1988 (Box 28:754)
      - 189 (Box 29:755)
      - 1990 (Box 29:756)
      - 1991 (Box 29:757)
      - 1992 January 27 - 1997 November 3 (Box 29:758)
    - Denials of declassification and MR benefits, undated, 1981-1991 (Box 29:759)
    - Requests to government agencies and presidential libraries for declassification of documents (includes mandatory review requests); on Cuba (for book, Contesting Castro
      - undated, 1980 - 1982 November 30 (Box 29:760)
      - 1983 (Box 29:761)
      - 1984 (Box 29:762)
      - 1985 (Box 29:763)
      - 1986-1996 (Box 29:764)
    - FBI FOIA deleted pages sheets (indicating withdrawal deletion of documents) relating to documents on Cuba (for book Contesting Castro 1950s)
      - undated, 1961 January 17 - 1986 April 2 (Box 29:765)
      - undated, 1961 January 16 - 1985 October 23 (Box 29:766)
      - undated, 1978 April 3 - 1985 June 11 (Box 29:767)
      - undated, 1978 April 3-7 (Box 29:768)
      - undated, 1956 January 30 - 1986 February 10 (Box 29:769)
      - undated, 1978 April 4 - May (Box 29:770)
      - undated, 1978 April 4 - 1985 September 13 (Box 29:771)
      - undated, 1985 June 4 (Box 29:772)
      - undated, 1978 March 31 - 1986 January 10 (Box 29:773)
- Series VII: Photographs, negatives and microfiche, undated, 1944-1968
  - Photographs
    - Allen, George V., undated, 1946-1968 (Box 29:774)
    - American Foreign Policy (1st ed.), undated (Box 29:775)